<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Workout</string>
    <string name="swim">Swimming is a popular aquatic sport and recreational activity that involves propelling oneself through water using the arms and legs. It is also a form of exercise that provides a full-body workout and has many health benefits. Swimming can be done in various environments such as pools, lakes, rivers, and oceans. Swimming strokes include freestyle, backstroke, breaststroke, and butterfly. Freestyle is the most commonly used stroke in competitive swimming and is also referred to as the front crawl. Backstroke involves swimming on the back, breaststroke involves a frog-like kicking motion, and butterfly involves a dolphin-like swimming technique.</string>
    <string name="jump">Jumping is the act of propelling oneself off the ground using one or both legs. It is a basic human movement and is involved in many sports and activities, such as basketball, volleyball, and dance. Jumping can be done in various ways, including vertical jumps, broad jumps, and long jumps. Vertical jumps involve jumping as high as possible from a stationary position, while broad jumps involve jumping as far as possible from a standing position. Long jumps involve running and jumping as far as possible from a starting line. Jumping can provide numerous physical benefits, such as increasing lower body strength, power, and explosiveness. It can also improve cardiovascular fitness, balance, and coordination. Additionally, jumping can be a fun and challenging activity that can improve mental focus and reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="run">Running is a form of exercise and physical activity that involves moving at a fast pace using the legs and feet. It is a popular form of cardiovascular exercise that provides a full-body workout and numerous health benefits. Running can be done outdoors or indoors on a treadmill. Running is a natural human movement and can be performed at various speeds, distances, and terrains. Some people run for recreation, while others engage in competitive running events such as marathons, triathlons, and track and field competitions.</string>
</resources>